<?xml version="1.0"?>
<metadata xml:lang="en"><Esri><CreaDate>20201110</CreaDate><CreaTime>16052200</CreaTime><ArcGISFormat>1.0</ArcGISFormat><SyncOnce>TRUE</SyncOnce><ModDate>20201110</ModDate><ModTime>18100400</ModTime><scaleRange><minScale>150000000</minScale><maxScale>5000</maxScale></scaleRange></Esri><tool name="esriSync" displayname="Esri Synchronize" toolboxalias="" xmlns=""><arcToolboxHelpPath>c:\program files\arcgis\pro\Resources\Help\gp</arcToolboxHelpPath><parameters><param name="Target_Metadata" displayname="Target Feature Class" type="Required" direction="Input" datatype="Multiple Value" expression="Target_Metadata;Target_Metadata..."><dialogReference>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;The feature class to perform synchronization.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</dialogReference></param><param name="SyncOption" displayname="Synchronize Option" type="Required" direction="Input" datatype="String" expression="SELECTIVE | OVERWRITE"><dialogReference>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN STYLE="font-weight:bold;"&gt;SELECTIVE&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt; —Generally the same as the OVERWRITE option. However, the values of the Title and Content Type metadata elements are not updated. For example, if you import a standard-format metadata document to the item that describes the item's data, the title in the imported document does apply to the item, and it will not be overwritten. All other properties in the item's metadata will be initialized in a manner appropriate for the item. Metadata content will be updated appropriately at the time the function is used; a time specified by the interval parameter is not used, if one has been provided. Metadata is created if it doesn't already exist.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN STYLE="font-weight:bold;"&gt;OVERWRITE&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt; —All property values that can be synchronized are updated in the item's metadata, regardless of the value or presence of the Sync attribute on these metadata elements. After this function is used, all metadata elements that have been updated will have a Sync attribute with the value True. For example, after copying metadata from one item to another, use this option to initialize all properties in a manner that is appropriate for the item, including the title, which should be changed to match the new item's name instead of using a title that describes the old item. Metadata content will be updated appropriately at the time the function is used; a time specified by the interval parameter is not used, if one has been provided. Metadata is created if it doesn't already exist.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</dialogReference></param></parameters><summary>&lt;DIV STYLE="text-align:Left;"&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;DIV&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;This tool uses Esri's Metadata Synchronizer with additional options available only via python. Please refer to Esri's &lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;A href="https://pro.arcgis.com:443/en/pro-app/arcpy/metadata/metadata-class.htm" STYLE="text-decoration:underline;"&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;documentation&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/A&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt; for details. https://pro.arcgis.com/en/pro-app/arcpy/metadata/metadata-class.htm&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;From Esri:&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;If the Metadata object represents a feature class's metadata, this function will update the metadata content to reflect current properties of the data, such as the number of features it has, its spatial reference, the current list of attributes, and so on. If the item doesn't have any metadata content, it may or may not be created for the item, depending on the metadata_sync_option. Also, the interval time is considered, depending on the metadata_sync_option.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;P&gt;&lt;SPAN&gt;Some metadata elements should always be derived from the item's properties, such as its spatial reference. Some metadata elements can be initialized by the properties of the item, but would typically be updated by a person to better characterize the item before the metadata is shared, such the title of the item. The metadata_sync_option determines which properties of the item are updated, and how metadata elements are handled if a person has typed a value in that element.&lt;/SPAN&gt;&lt;/P&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;&lt;/DIV&gt;</summary></tool><dataIdInfo><idCitation><resTitle>Esri Synchronize</resTitle></idCitation><idCredit>Esri, https://pro.arcgis.com/en/pro-app/arcpy/metadata/metadata-class.htm</idCredit></dataIdInfo><distInfo><distributor><distorFormat><formatName>ArcToolbox Tool</formatName></distorFormat></distributor></distInfo><mdHrLv><ScopeCd value="005"/></mdHrLv><mdDateSt Sync="FALSE">2020-11-10</mdDateSt></metadata>
